this tutorial is back flaps so here we
本教程是后襟翼，所以在这里我们
你有两种吗
this tutorial is back flaps so here we
are there's two kinds this kind as you
拉舌尖朝方向拉
极点非常容易
are there's two kinds this kind as you
pull the tab tip pulls in the direction
结构和这种类型更多
拉动标签时有趣
pull the tab tip pulls in the direction
of the pole it's a very very easy
在与杆相反的方向
我先做一对夫妇
of the pole it's a very very easy
structure and this type is more
这里的第一个是拉带
基本的拉条在
structure and this type is more
interesting as you pull the tab it moves
教程25，因此所有拉带都必须
他们还需要两倍的厚度
interesting as you pull the tab it moves
in the opposite direction to the pole
测量，所以我已经完成了所有测量
事先准备好这些东西
I'll just start by making a couple the
只是为了使其更快，所以这是
游泳池地带，它已经被记分了
I'll just start by making a couple the
first one here it is the pull strip the
中间折叠，然后总是粘上
当它要折叠在里面时
first one here it is the pull strip the
basic pull strip is explained in
粘在一起就可以使整个事情变得完整
更强大，所以你可以推它拉它没有
basic pull strip is explained in
tutorial 25 and so all pull strips must
屈曲，这是拉力带
两倍的厚度，然后在末尾
tutorial 25 and so all pull strips must
be double thickness they also need
厚度，你只有这个小标签
这就是要坚持的
be double thickness they also need
measuring so I've done all the measuring
拍拍并提起它，这是拍拍我
准备好的襟翼上有一个标签
measuring so I've done all the measuring
and prepared these pieces beforehand
会粘在页面上的底部
以及我测量的位置
and prepared these pieces beforehand
just to make it quicker so this is the
将标签上的胶水粘到
页拉带将坚持
just to make it quicker so this is the
pool strip it's been scored down the
在这里穿过这两个缝隙
切开缝的页面，这样
pool strip it's been scored down the
middle folded and then always glue it
他们往回走了一点，他们只
需要回去
middle folded and then always glue it
when it's going to fold in it and it's
汽车刚刚举起的两餐
向上，但只有一点点
when it's going to fold in it and it's
glued it just makes the whole thing
需要减少约一厘米
所以它可以提起更多，所以你只喂
glued it just makes the whole thing
stronger so you can push it pull it no
通过它通过这一面
好，然后我们就可以贴上标签了
stronger so you can push it pull it no
buckling and this one the pull strip is
顶部，但我认为这自然而然
在下面，所以对您隐藏了
buckling and this one the pull strip is
double thickness and then at the end one
在那个上面放一些胶水然后粘下来
让它熄灭，是的，你去看看
double thickness and then at the end one
thickness you just have this little tab
提升了流程，还有另一个
地带去的方式
thickness you just have this little tab
which is what's going to stick onto the
通过皮瓣，有一个很好的
罗伯特·凯特斯（Robert Crafters）这本书中的例子
which is what's going to stick onto the
flap and lift it up this is the flap I
最惊人的捉迷藏计数书
如果我们打开它，那是我们
flap and lift it up this is the flap I
prepared the flap has a tab on the
看着你拉它抬起
襟翼，实际上还有另一个
prepared the flap has a tab on the
bottom that that will stick to the page
拍打在下面，所以你可以看到
被推过那里有一个插槽
bottom that that will stick to the page
and the place I've measured it to be put
皮瓣再次在这里，坡度将
大约两毫米宽
and the place I've measured it to be put
the glue on the tab and glue it to the
构造这里有折痕
所以这两个位已经
the glue on the tab and glue it to the
page the pull strip is going to stick on
折叠并推入插槽
主瓣，然后再次展开
page the pull strip is going to stick on
here and go through these two slits in
然后通过这个目的
页面，这只是
here and go through these two slits in
the page the slits need to be cut so
这种类型
另一种更有趣
the page the slits need to be cut so
they go back a bit this end they only
真的是这种类型的东西
从游泳池的方向，它是
they go back a bit this end they only
need to go back
基于地球，我想开槽
页面的支点我有一个更大的
need to go back
couple of meals that the car just lifts
在这里，您可以更清楚地看到它
地带上有两个小标签
couple of meals that the car just lifts
up and very little bit but this but it
两侧，当你
将整个东西推过这个插槽
up and very little bit but this but it
needs to be cut back about a centimeter
然后您展开它们，它们保持
整件事
needs to be cut back about a centimeter
so it can lift up more so you just feed
这是我准备的那个
拉条双厚度
so it can lift up more so you just feed
it through feed it through this side as
所以我就用胶水粘上
双倍厚度的拉条，现在在这里
it through feed it through this side as
well and then we can stick the tab on
这是两个小标签
向下折叠，因为你可以撑起整个
well and then we can stick the tab on
top but I think it's just nature it goes
件这是这里的另一折
是什么使整个事情起作用
top but I think it's just nature it goes
underneath so it's hidden from you put
重要的是在这一点之间
在小标签和主标签之间
underneath so it's hidden from you put
some glue on that one and stick it down
拍打这点，这点在哪里
折痕是大约七百万
let it go off and yep there you go see
相当关键，你有主襟翼
然后有两个小标签
let it go off and yep there you go see
it's lifting the flow there is another
折叠起来并通过
插入页面，然后再次展开
it's lifting the flow there is another
way of doing this where the strip goes
其余的带穿过
缝在这里，你把它们折叠下来
way of doing this where the strip goes
through the flap and there's a good
是个荡妇而不是缝，所以这是两个或
三毫米宽，而这是一个
through the flap and there's a good
example in this Robert crafters book the
切开它就直切
页面，以便您可以将其折叠
example in this Robert crafters book the
most amazing hide-and-seek counting book
通过页面的整个过程，以及
然后将它们展开到另一侧
most amazing hide-and-seek counting book
and if we open it up this is one we're
现在把它固定在这个位置上
来到这里，这给你
and if we open it up this is one we're
looking at as you pull it it lifts up
动作动作是我第一本书
想要告诉你海伦的丛林时代
looking at as you pull it it lifts up
the flap and it's actually got another
理发师，这是皮瓣的类型
远离方向
the flap and it's actually got another
flap underneath so you can see this has
拉，并有一个图像附加到
因此，当您拉动它时，襟翼会抬起
flap underneath so you can see this has
been pushed through there's a slot in
和鳄鱼跳
你看着它就可以看到
been pushed through there's a slot in
the flap here again the slope will be
在它下面有一个皮瓣
远离方向
the flap here again the slope will be
about two millimeters wide and to
拉条然后得到图像
附加到它和我们拥有的另一种类型
about two millimeters wide and to
construct this there are creases here
看着这里就是这个类型
襟翼在
construct this there are creases here
and here so these two bits have been
拉条的方向，使您
拉它下来那是另一个
and here so these two bits have been
folded up and pushed through the slot in
我想给你看的另一本书
这是一个很有趣的变化
folded up and pushed through the slot in
the main flap and then unfolded again
这是小红帽的
布鲁斯·福斯特（Bruce Foster），在这种情况下，这是一个
the main flap and then unfolded again
and then this end is pushed through that
襟翼和这些是选项卡，但相反
拉环以使平板平坦
and then this end is pushed through that
page so that's just another variation of
移动你抬起皮瓣，它使
标签光滑，你拉下皮瓣，
page so that's just another variation of
this type
这些向上移动，然后在这种情况下
襟翼必须在其下方折叠
the other kind which is more interesting
下一个我想告诉你的是
颜色使一些法国苦力感到惊讶
the other kind which is more interesting
really is this type which lifts up away
大卫·佩洛姆（David Pellom）和这个人感到惊讶
这是公寓的类型
really is this type which lifts up away
from the direction of the pool and it's
襟翼移离
拉的方向，在这种情况下
from the direction of the pool and it's
based on earth I guess the slotting the
在下面有几折
它的主要负责人是
based on earth I guess the slotting the
pages of fulcrum I've got a bigger one
平行折叠，然后你有两个
V形折叠，每边都很漂亮
pages of fulcrum I've got a bigger one
here so you can see it much more clearly
下一个我想告诉你的是
Lampe和Kowski的机器人这是两个
here so you can see it much more clearly
the strip has these two little tabs on
拍打在一根杆子上，当您拉动它时
一种接近的类型
the strip has these two little tabs on
each side and they fold up while you
拉的方向和这个
朝相反的方向走
each side and they fold up while you
push the whole thing through this slot
拉它，他们都举起，这有
它下面有一个V形折叠
push the whole thing through this slot
then you unfold them and they keep the
它下面的平行折叠相当不错
我想给你看一些例子
then you unfold them and they keep the
whole thing in position
我有更多的这些是
只是您如何做的一个非常简单的例子
whole thing in position
here's the one I prepared this is the
可以使两个襟翼一起工作
你看它的背面，只是
here's the one I prepared this is the
pull strip double-thickness
带钢是双重的，你可以看到所有
很清楚，虽然这是
pull strip double-thickness
so I'll just glue that so that's the
您已经将襟翼移离了
游泳池的方向，但在这种情况下
so I'll just glue that so that's the
double thickness pull strip and now here
它有一个
内置在其背面的平行四边形
double thickness pull strip and now here
these are the two little tabs which will
它会弹出在
这样在这里您可以看到
these are the two little tabs which will
fold down as you can strut the whole
平行四边形可以看到动作
在页面下方，您可以将其抬起
fold down as you can strut the whole
piece this is a another fold here which
现在有两个标签
碰到这个缝并停止它
piece this is a another fold here which
is what makes the whole thing work the
移动使它停止时处于停止状态
延迟的垂直位置
is what makes the whole thing work the
important thing is to between this point
双重动作，所以更多
当您先拉条时很复杂
important thing is to between this point
between the little tabs and the main
一个皮瓣举起，然后另一个皮瓣举起
这种襟翼的工作原理实际上是
between the little tabs and the main
flap this point and this point where the
一个口袋，不只是一张卡片
它实际上是空心的，所以当
flap this point and this point where the
crease is that's about seven mil that's
你可以这样看
实际看到拉条的末端
crease is that's about seven mil that's
fairly crucial you have the main flap
在口袋里向上拉
它提起它，然后
fairly crucial you have the main flap
and then you have these two little tabs
向后滑动第二个襟翼
这一块，这些通过这个
and then you have these two little tabs
which fold up and go through the
页面中的窗口，以便您拖动它
最初不参与，必须走
which fold up and go through the
slotting the page and then unfold again
那么远
然后它可以接合并举起第二个
slotting the page and then unfold again
and the rest of the strip goes through
拍打，所以这里的关键是
两只皮瓣之间的距离
and the rest of the strip goes through
this slit here you fold them down this
正在通过页面上的插槽工作
所以在这里您可以看到
this slit here you fold them down this
is a not a slit so this is two or
页面之间的距离是
与此折痕之间的距离相同
is a not a slit so this is two or
three millimeters wide whereas this is a
这一点在窗口中
滑动它接合的地方，这就是
three millimeters wide whereas this is a
slit it's just it's straight cutting the
一件至关重要的事情，我可以
给你展示一个很好的例子
slit it's just it's straight cutting the
page so you can fold those down you push
在行动中，这是幼年牡丹的机器人
科夫斯基这就是你的这头蛇头
page so you can fold those down you push
the whole thing through the page and
首先拉舌片舌头出来
然后你继续拉，然后
the whole thing through the page and
then you unfold them on the other side
蛇头抬起，眼睛在
建在襟翼上，您可能会很有用
then you unfold them on the other side
that's now holding it in position this
从侧面看
你可以看到达是什么时候
that's now holding it in position this
comes through here and that gives you
首先，舌头消失，然后
头去，眼睛
comes through here and that gives you
the moving action the first book I'd
翻过来，我还想要一个
告诉你这是爱丽丝
the moving action the first book I'd
like to show you is jungle days by Helen
仙境与造纸工程
我是罗杰·迪亚兹（Roger Diaz）的那个
like to show you is jungle days by Helen
barber and this is the type of flap that
在抬起页面时查看
条实际上是翻过皮瓣
barber and this is the type of flap that
moves away from the direction of the
这是自动拉带
我想用拍打动作
moves away from the direction of the
pull and it's got an image attached to
自动池剥离是教程16
这是关于襟翼的本教程
pull and it's got an image attached to
it so as you pull it the flap lifts up
在这些中有更多关于它们的信息
我的两本书是最
it so as you pull it the flap lifts up
and the crocodile jump
最近一项弹出式设计和论文
力学上有更多关于襟翼的信息
and the crocodile jump
you look at it end on you can see
那里有更多关于拉
本书中的条带弹出了
you look at it end on you can see
there's the flap underneath it that's
纸机制这是第一本书
我做到了，关于拉动标签有很多
there's the flap underneath it that's
moving away from the direction of the
在里面
您
moving away from the direction of the
pull strip then it's got the image